

#### **PROFILE**

My dedication to learning new things is a significant advantage in my professional life. This allows me to work effectively and collaboratively, while also enhancing my skills and knowledge in the IT industry.

Having just a year of experience as a developer is not a hindrance to accomplishing client requirements. Instead, it motivates me to produce high-quality results.

#### CONTACT

PHONE: 09179914429

Portfolio: JCP - Portfolio

LikedIn:

www.linkedin.com/in/johnchristopher-pesquera-948049230

christopherpesquera 123@gmail.com

## **HOBBIES**

Playing video games Playing guitar Listening to music

# JOHN CHRISTOPHER PESQUERA

Software Engineer

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# SEBI Technologies Inc. - Software Engineer

August 2023 – Present

School Management System

- Able to work with large amount of data and use it in the development accordingly.
- Able to work with QA's and fixed issued depending on their assessments.
- Able to deal with client requirements.
- Enhanced skills by creating dynamic and reusable code which can be used by other developers.

## SEBI Technologies Inc. - Software Engineer Intern

February 2023 – May 2023 Payroll System

- Developed lookup modules that are necessary for the system.
- Able to migrate old system to new approach of development.
- Able to work collaboratively with other intern and employees.

# **EDUCATION**

#### Technological Institute of the Philippines

2019-2023

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology Graduated with distinction

#### Parana Hiah School

2018-2019

Graduated with Honors

## **SKILLS**

- Html and CSS
- VueJS Framework
- Php
- Laravel
- GraphQL
- REST API

- PostgreSQL Knowledgeable in:
- React JS
- Ionic Framework
- Unity
  - C#

# **SEMINARS ATTENDED**

- Project Management Tool Training using JIRA Software Webinar (2021)
- Artificial Intelligence from A-Z: Fundamentals of Data Science and Beyond (2022)
- Intelligent and Professional Interaction (2022)